<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>INTRODUCING THE DEMO on Castlelore Studios</title>
    <link>https://castlelorestudios.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in INTRODUCING THE DEMO on Castlelore Studios</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2025 Castlelore Studios LLC</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:48:36 -1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://castlelorestudios.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Pitch Deck</title>
      <link>https://castlelorestudios.com/pitch-deck/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 10:48:36 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://castlelorestudios.com/pitch-deck/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;pitch-xoru-the-nightmare-wars-demo&#34;&gt;Pitch: Xoru The Nightmare Wars (Demo)&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-cover--concept-&#34;&gt;1. Cover &amp;amp; Concept 🎮&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;title-working-xoru-the-nightmare-wars&#34;&gt;Title (Working): Xoru: The Nightmare Wars&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tagline:&lt;/strong&gt; “What Is Real, What Is Not, and What Matters.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Genre:&lt;/strong&gt; Narrative-driven Isekai RPG / stealth puzzle adventure&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;2-team--expertise&#34;&gt;2. Team &amp;amp; Expertise&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Creative Director / Writer: Expert in hero’s journey narratives,&#xA;branching dialogue, moral ambiguity&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Narrative Designers: Skilled in subversive narration and multi‑path storylines&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Level &amp;amp; Puzzle Designers: Experienced with mirror‑box style mazes,&#xA;trap logic, stealth routes&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Demo</title>
      <link>https://castlelorestudios.com/demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 23:21:30 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://castlelorestudios.com/demo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://widgets.gamejolt.com/package/v1?key=RkxzrD7q&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; width=&#34;500&#34;&#xA;        height=&#34;245&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;iframe width=&#34;600&#34; height=&#34;180&#34; src=&#34;https://www.indiedb.com/games/xoru-the-nightmare-wars/widget&#34;&#xA;        frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.indiedb.com/games/xoru-the-nightmare-wars&#34;&gt;Xoru: The Nightmare&#xA;        Wars Demo game - IndieDB&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;    &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://store.steampowered.com/widget/3431270/&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;100%&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;iframe frameborder=&#34;0&#34;&#xA;        src=&#34;https://itch.io/embed/3199147?bg_color=222222&amp;amp;fg_color=eeeeee&amp;amp;link_color=b92ed8&amp;amp;border_color=363636&#34;&#xA;        width=&#34;100%&#34; height=&#34;100%&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://castlelorestudios.itch.io/xoru-nightmare-wars&#34;&gt;Xoru: Nightmare Wars&#xA;            Demo by Castlelore Studios LLC&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Player</title>
      <link>https://castlelorestudios.com/player/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:19:27 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://castlelorestudios.com/player/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;He left on a morning that broke gray. No note. No goodbye. Just the soft clack of boots on frost and the knowledge that if he looked back, he’d never leave.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;War welcomed him with a laugh and a sword.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He signed his name—then gave it up. In the ranks, names didn’t matter. Only how well you bled. He became a number, then a voice, then a shadow. By the second Iokela campaign, he was leading charges. By the third, he was choosing those who wouldn’t come home.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barbarian</title>
      <link>https://castlelorestudios.com/barbarian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:19:23 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://castlelorestudios.com/barbarian/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;He was born to the Clan Varosk, one of the oldest Laconic bloodlines still bound to the stoneflower groves of Wilderburrow. Centaur in form, but more than myth—he was carved of thunder and sacred vows. His people do not name children until they’ve survived five winters and five tests. When his time came, he stood in the river for three nights and did not sleep.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://castlelorestudios.com/images/barbarian.png&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h4&gt;Barbarian&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They called him Titus Storm-Walker, but only in the old tongue. To the world beyond Wilderburrow, he became Barbarian. A name born of ignorance—and earned through fear.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vizious</title>
      <link>https://castlelorestudios.com/vizious/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:16:21 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://castlelorestudios.com/vizious/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;He excelled. Not because he wanted to. Because he had no other way to exist.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In time, he became one of the youngest Leximancers ever initiated into the Circle of Intent—those who believed language could reshape reality. Glyph-magic. Will-script. It was beautiful. Dangerous. And so very close to divine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And then he met her. And a half-circle became whole.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://castlelorestudios.com/images/vizious_center_face.png&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h4&gt;Vizious&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;seren&#34;&gt;Seren.&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She wasn’t smarter. But she was braver. Where he obeyed, she questioned. Where he hesitated, she walked. She once told him that truth wasn’t in books, but in the breath between two people brave enough to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lila</title>
      <link>https://castlelorestudios.com/lila/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:16:18 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://castlelorestudios.com/lila/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lila was born in the harbor-city of Kezmarin, among the pirate-haunted Seven Eyes, where fog wrapped towers like memory and every alley hummed with secrets. Her mother was a mapmaker once, long retired, her hands bent from old compass work and ink stains. Her father died young—some said at sea, others whispered darker things. Lila never asked. What she cared about was her uncle.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://castlelorestudios.com/images/lila-disbelief.png&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h4&gt;Lila&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Taro.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He was the kind of man who arrived like storms—sudden, loud, always with salt in his hair and laughter in his mouth. He brought her gifts from forgotten ports and stories from sunken ruins. He taught her how to pick locks without shame, how to read a sky for secrets, and how to lie only when the truth might hurt worse.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gerrick</title>
      <link>https://castlelorestudios.com/gerrick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 11:15:26 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://castlelorestudios.com/gerrick/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gerrick’s earliest memories were not of light or sanctuary, but of ash. He came from a famine-wracked highland Sunthorne village called Lostwood —barely more than a scar of thatch and rock clinging to the throat of the Sunthorne Mountains. His father was a stonemason with cracked knuckles and a voice that never rose above a whisper. His mother died the winter after his ninth summer, her bones picked quiet by cold and plague.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Character Biographies</title>
      <link>https://castlelorestudios.com/character-bios/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 18:19:12 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://castlelorestudios.com/character-bios/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;gerrick&#34;&gt;Gerrick&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He was not born into faith.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He was carved into it, like a name chiseled into stone by hands not his own. &lt;a href=&#34;https://castlelorestudios.com/gerrick/&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;more-link&#34;&gt;MORE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;lila&#34;&gt;Lila&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;She never meant to chase ghosts. But the sea teaches hunger before it teaches peace. &lt;a href=&#34;https://castlelorestudios.com/lila/&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;more-link&#34;&gt;MORE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;vizious&#34;&gt;Vizious&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He was born beneath a dome of mirrored stone, where the walls whispered spells older than the sun.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vizious was not his birth name. That one he buried long ago—along with the boy who wanted to heal things. His family were acolytes of the Archive Temple of Noctherein in Dol Marris, a city of scholars built atop the ribcage of a dead god. They didn’t raise him so much as assign him. Tutors for every hour. Recitations in lieu of lullabies. Even love, when it came, was wrapped in riddles and footnotes. &lt;a href=&#34;https://castlelorestudios.com/vizious/&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;more-link&#34;&gt;MORE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Moraduum</title>
      <link>https://castlelorestudios.com/moraduum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 15:58:16 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://castlelorestudios.com/moraduum/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;moraduum-the-dreamweavers-shadow&#34;&gt;Moraduum: The Dreamweaver’s Shadow&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moraduum is not merely an external antagonist—it is the severed shadow of the Dreamweaver himself. Once a mortal who ascended to guard the veil between waking and dream, the Dreamweaver sought to balance all things: light and dark, memory and forgetting, suffering and solace.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But part of him resisted.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That part became Moraduum: a cast-off fragment of soul too volatile, too consumed with sorrow and futility, to bear the burden of cosmic stewardship. It sees memory as a cruelty, and dreams as cages. Where the Dreamweaver seeks to preserve meaning, Moraduum seeks to dissolve it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Prologue</title>
      <link>https://castlelorestudios.com/prologue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 23:48:14 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://castlelorestudios.com/prologue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;gerrick&#34;&gt;Gerrick&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Gerrick knelt in silence, not to pray—but to keep the names from vanishing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;There were more now. More than he could mark in a single night. But he tried anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The stone beneath his knees was cold, worn by weather and the friction of ritual. The roof above had collapsed years ago, maybe in a storm, maybe under the weight of forgotten faith. The altar had crumbled. The benches had rotted. And yet, Gerrick remained. Paladin. Oathkeeper. Or something lesser, depending on who told the story.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Shape of Xoru</title>
      <link>https://castlelorestudios.com/shape-of-xoru/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 22:10:51 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://castlelorestudios.com/shape-of-xoru/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Shape of Xoru is a dark, mythic exploration of a fractured world haunted by the remnants of dreams and nightmares. Once unified by peace and meaning, Xoru is now torn by a mysterious rift between two realms.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;the-shape-of-xoru&#34;&gt;The Shape of Xoru&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They say the world used to be one.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Not in the way of geography or empire, but in how it felt, how breath moved through it, how sleep came without fear. There were dreams then, yes. But they were soft things. Maps of the soul. Not traps. Not teeth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Soulful Steelyard</title>
      <link>https://castlelorestudios.com/soulful-steelyard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 22:10:29 -1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://castlelorestudios.com/soulful-steelyard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-soulful-steelyard&#34;&gt;The Soulful Steelyard&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A whispered mechanism. A dream-forged machine. A weight that must always be borne.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It is not seen with eyes but felt in the soul&amp;rsquo;s marrow—this Steelyard. Half symbol, half construct, it was shaped in the first moments of the Sunrise Age, when the world still remembered the gods, and Light sought to hold its ground against the long night.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://castlelorestudios.com/images/steelyard.webp&#34;&gt;&lt;figcaption&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h4&gt;The Soulful Steelyard&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/figcaption&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;They say the powers of Light could not destroy the Darkness outright—only measure it. And so, beneath the world, behind the veil, they built the Steelyard. A vast and hidden scale, metaphysical in purpose but real enough to bleed. It balances virtue and vice, and when it falters, so too does the Dreamweaver—the living fulcrum of the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
